Guide to the Benoit Mandelbrot Papers M1857
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 6. Loose Correspondence, 1947-2011
  - Correspondence - 2006 (Box 189, Folders 4-10)
  - Correspondence - 2006 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 2006 (Box 294, Folders 1-7)
  - Correspondence - 2006 (Box 295, Folders 1-5)
  - Correspondence - 2007 (Box 295, Folders 6-8)
  - Correspondence - 2007 (Box 296, Folders 1-7)
  - Correspondence - 2007 (Box 297, Folders 1-2)
  - Correspondence - 2007 (Box 190, Folders 2-10)
  - Correspondence - 2008 (Box 297, Folders 3-7)
  - Correspondence - 2008 (Box 298, Folders 1-5)
  - Correspondence - 2008 (Box 190, Folders 11-13)
  - Correspondence - 2008 (Box 191, Folders 1-6)
  - Correspondence - 2009 (Box 298, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 2009 (Box 191, Folders 7-9)
  - Correspondence - 2009 (Box 192, Folders 1-5)
  - Correspondence - 2010 (Box 298, Folders 7-9)
  - Correspondence - 2010 (Box 299, Folders 1-4)
  - Correspondence - 2010 (Box 192, Folders 6-11)
  - Correspondence - 2010-2011 (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 2011 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - undated (Box 299, Folder 7)
- Series 7. Books
  This series consists of materials related to Mandelbrot's books, including stand-alone monographs and Selecta - compilations of Mandelbrot's published articles, sometimes adding new material and commentary. Materials include pasted up boards; handwritten, typescript and computer printout drafts, many heavily edited; camera copies; galleys; and correspondence.
  - Subseries 1. Les Objets Fractals: Form, Hasard et Dimension, 1974-2002
    This subseries consists of materials related to Les Objets Fractals: Form, Hasard et Dimension, first published in 1975. Materials include edited drafts, page mock-ups, galleys, correspondence and book jackets. This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - Objets physiques de dimension fractionnaire - "epreuves corrigees incompletement" (edited draft), circa 1974 Jan 22 (from box labeled "important - 1st objets fractal before the name fractal") (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Objets Concrets de Dimension Fractionnaire (photocopy of page mock-up), 1974 (from box labeled "important - 1st objets fractal before the name fractal") (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Objets physiques de dimension fractionnaire - "early 1975 book" - heavily edited drafts (Box 237, Folder 16)
    - Objets physiques de dimension fractionnaire - heavily edited drafts, circa mid 1970s (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - Nouveau livre francais - Versatec, 1983 Mar (Les Objets Fractals, deuxieme edition; edited draft) (Box 169, Folders 1-2)
    - Nouveau livre francais - APS, 1983 Apr ( Les Objets Fractals, deuxieme edition; edited draft) (Box 169, Folders 3-4)
    - Nouveau livre francais - APS-5, 1983 May ( Les Objets Fractals, deuxieme edition; edited draft) (Box 169, Folders 5-6)
    - Les Objets Fractals - deuxieme edition - preface and references (multiple handwritten/computer printout drafts, edited), 1983 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Les Objets Fractals - "exemplaire a conserver" (contains corrections for 2nd edition), 1983 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Les Objets Fractals - deuxieme edition - Audibert, 1983 May - 1984 Mar (edited draft) (Box 170, Folders 4-5)
    - Les Objets Fractals - deuxieme edition, 1984 (edited drafts) (Box 169, Folders 8-10)
    - Les Objets Fractals: Forme, Hasard et Dimension, suvie d'un survol du langage fractal, circa 1987 (edited chapter drafts) (Box 170, Folders 6-7)
    - Les Objets Fractals, 3rd edition, circa 1988-1989 (edited computer printout drafts) (Box 171, Folders 4-5)
    - Les Objets Fractals, 3rd edition, circa 1988-1989 (edited computer printout drafts) (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Les Objets Fractals, 3rd edition, circa 1988-1989 (edited computer printout drafts) (Box 172, Folders 2-3)
    - Les Objets Fractals, 3rd edition, circa 1989 (edited computer printout drafts) (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Les Objets Fractals, 3rd edition, circa 1989 (edited computer printout drafts) (Box 171, Folders 1-3)
    - Les Objets Fractals - objects et images fractals [3rd edition?], circa 1980s (edited computer printout drafts) (Box 172, Folders 4-5)
    - Les Objets Fractals - Portuguese translation (correspondence, agreements), 1990-1991 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Conjectures concerning turbulent dispersion - handwritten/computer printout drafts, undated (Box 237, Folder 17)
    - Les Objets Fractals, quatrieme edition, 1995 (galley with minor edits) (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Les Objets Fractals - edited chapter draft - Les distributions de probabilite L-stables, circa 2001 (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Les Objets Fractals - correspondence and plates regarding Brazilian/Portuguese versions, 2001-2002 (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Les Objets Fractals - edited computer printout draft, undated (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Les Objets Fractals - edited computer printout of partial draft, undated (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - Les Objets Fractals - book jackets, undated (Box 247, Folder 12)
    - Les Objets Fractals - book jacket, undated (Box 303, Folder 9)
    - Les Objets Fractals - book reviews, undated (Box 247, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 2. Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension, 1975-1979
    This subseries consists of materials related to Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension, first published in 1977. Materials include edited drafts, camera copies, page mock-ups, reviews, pasted up boards, original plates and book kits. This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - Book 1975 (early) and Judith's translation (heavily edited computer printout drafts) (Box 22, Folders 1-2)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - edited manuscript drafts and computer printouts of early chapter drafts, circa 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folders 1-7)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - edited manuscript drafts and computer printouts of early chapter drafts, circa 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folders 1-5)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - 1976 manuscript and Marsden comments (Box 317, Folders 1-2)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - heavily edited handwritten/computer printout drafts, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folders 1-7)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - heavily edited handwritten/computer printout drafts, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folders 1-7)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - heavily edited handwritten/computer printout drafts, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folders 1-3)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - Chapter XII - Mathematical Lexicon and Addenda (edited computer printout draft), 1977 Jan 27 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - 1977 complete camera copy - text, no art (Box 317, Folders 3-7)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - rough copy of page mock-up before final art was inserted, 1977 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - reduced rough copy of page mock-up before final art was inserted (photocopy) (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - 1979 edit (heavily edited computer printout drafts) (Box 22, Folders 3-4)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - 1979 edit (heavily edited computer printout chapter drafts from 1977 version, with new material) (Box 22, Folders 5-6)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - 1979 edit (heavily edited computer printout chapter drafts from 1977 version, with new material) (Box 23, Folders 1-6)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - book reviews, 1979 (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - edited partial drafts, circa late 1970s (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - reduced rough copy of page mock-up before final art was inserted - 2nd English ed (edited), circa late 1970s-early 1980s (Box 303)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - pasted up boards/original plates, undated (Box 39, Folders 5-6)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - book kit, undated (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension -Distribution list for review copies (Box 501, Folder 14)
    - Fractals: Form, Chance and Dimension - partial camera copy (plates) (Flat-box 348, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3. The Fractal Geometry of Nature, 1979-2000s
    This subseries consists of materials related to The Fractal Geometry of Nature, first published in 1982. Materials include edited drafts, camera copies, galleys, pasted up boards, original art/figures, proofs, promotional material, correspondence, order forms and book jackets.
    The projected second edition of The Fractal Geometry of Nature, which BBM worked on with Peter Renz, was not published by the time of BBM's death in 2010 - see Box 144 Folder 2 memo from Peter Renz in 2010 which provides more details in regards to what was covered, and where things stood at the time of BBM's death.
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - Peano Curves and Plane Filling Trees (edited drafts), 1979 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - heavily edited chapter drafts (handwritten and computer printout drafts) 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folders 5-7)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - heavily edited chapter drafts (handwritten and computer printout drafts) 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folders 1-6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts, proofs, handwritten drafts, notes, 1981 (Box 13, Folders 1-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts, proofs, handwritten drafts, notes, 1981 (Box 14, Folders 1-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts, proofs, handwritten drafts, notes, 1981 (Box 15, Folders 1-3)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts, 1981 Apr (Box 31, Folders 1-2)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts, 1981 Apr (Box 31, Folders 3-4)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts, 1981 Apr (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts, circa 1981 (Box 32, Folders 1-2)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts of chapter drafts, notes, reprints, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folders 4-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts of chapter drafts, notes, reprints, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folders 1-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printouts of chapter drafts, notes, reprints, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folders 1-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - edited computer printout drafts, 1981-1982 (Box 237, Folders 2-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - photocopy of clean galley, circa 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folders 3-4)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - camera copy (photocopy), circa 1981-1982 (Box 303, Folders 7-8)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - update added in the second printing (XII 1982) (edited draft) 1982 Nov 29 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - complete camera copy (original), circa 1982 (Box 18, Folders 1-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - photocopy of clean galley, circa 1982 (Box 32, Folders 5-6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - pasted up boards, original art/figures, transparencies, photocopies, circa 1982 (Box 18, Folders 6-7)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - pasted up boards, original art/figures, transparencies, photocopies, circa 1982 (Box 19, Folders 1-3)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - Author's first proofs, circa 1982 (Box 33, Folders 1-2)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - promotion in Library of Science, 1983 May (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - promotion, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - typos, 1984-1985 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - Ch. 8 with comments by Peter Renz; correspondence, 2001 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - drafts, notes, correspondence with Peter Renz, 2001 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - notes, partial draft with editor's annotations, 2001 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - heavily edited chapter drafts, circa 2001 (Box 33, Folders 4-7)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - heavily edited chapter drafts, circa 2001 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - heavily edited chapter drafts, circa 2001 (Box 34)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - 2nd ed., 2002 partial revision (includes email printouts, heavy edits by BBM and comments/edits by others; original order maintained), 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folders 2-6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - 2nd ed., 2002 partial revision (includes email printouts, heavy edits by BBM and comments/edits by others; original order maintained), 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folders 1-6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - 2nd ed., 2002 partial revision (includes email printouts, heavy edits by BBM and comments/edits by others; original order maintained), 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folders 1-5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - addenda, notes, letter from Peter Renz, 2002 Mar (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - multiple edited drafts of "Introductions to the problems, the tools and the manner," circa 2002 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - Ch. 1 drafts with annotations by Peter Renz, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - edited chapter drafts, 2003 (Box 141, Folders 7-8)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - edited chapter drafts, 2003 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - multiple chapter drafts for heavily revised version, 2003-2005 (Box 142, Folders 2-6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - multiple chapter drafts for heavily revised version, 2003-2005 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - Ch. 3-7, 10-12, 32, 36, 38 (edited), 2003-2005 (Box 143, Folders 2-7)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - Ch. 10 draft, circa early 2000s (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - Ch. 2 drafts with edits and correspondence by Michael Frame, circa 2000s (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - projected second edition - memo detailing work by BBM and Peter Renz on a second version of The Fractal Geometry of Nature; notes; edited drafts, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - chapter drafts, multiple versions (edited), undated (Box 144, Folders 3-6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - color plate section, undated (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - book order form, undated (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - book jackets, undated (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - book jacket (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - partial monograph (addenda, biographical notes, references, index), undated (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - "Kit 82 Book," undated (edited) (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - "Kit 82 Book - complete," undated (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - "Kit 82 Book - missing pages," undated (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - color plate section, undated (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - Chapter 7, Ted Schultz notes, undated (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - Chapter 39, undated (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - French reviews (Box 501, Folder 12)
    - The Fractal Geometry of Nature - Art mock-ups (Flat-box 477, Folders 1-3)
  - Subseries 4. Fractals, Graphics and Mathematics Education, edited by BBM and Michael Frame, 2001-2002
    This subseries consists of materials related to Fractals, Graphics and Mathematics Education, published in 2002. Materials include edited drafts, correspondence, book reviews and draft book jackets. This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - Fractals, Graphics and Mathematics Education - by BBM and Michael Frame (correspondence, edited drafts), 2001 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Fractals, Graphics and Mathematics Education - by BBM and Michael Frame - book reviews, 2002 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Fractals, Graphics and Mathematics Education - by BBM and Michael Frame - draft book jackets, circa 2002 (Box 315, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 5. The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence by BBM and Richard Hudson, 2001-2005
    This subseries consists of materials related to The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence, published in 2004. Materials include edited drafts, correspondence, clean galleys, book reviews, press materials and draft book jackets. This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - correspondence with co-author Rich Hudson and publisher The Perseus Books Group, 2001-2004 (Box 49, Folders 1-2)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - outline, book proposal, circa 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - clean partial draft, 2003 Sep (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - clean partial draft, 2003 Sep (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - misc. partial drafts (edited), correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Table of Contents (edited drafts), 2004 Feb (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Preface (edited drafts), 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Prelude "Introducing a Maverick in Science" (edited drafts), 2004 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 1. Risk, Ruin and Reward (edited drafts), 2004 Jan (Box 50, Folders 1-2)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Interlude 1. Seeing is Believing (edited drafts), 2004 Jan (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 2. By the Toss of a Coin or the Flight of an Arrow (edited drafts), 2004 (Box 50, Folders 4-5)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 3. Bachelier and His Legacy (edited drafts), 2004 Jan (Box 50, Folders 6-7)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 4. The House of Modern Finance (edited drafts), 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folders 8-9)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 5. The Case Against the Modern Theory of Finance (edited drafts), 2004 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 6. Turbulent Markets: A Preview (edited drafts), 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 7. Studies in Roughness: A Fractal Primer (edited drafts), 2004 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 8. The Mystery of Cotton (edited drafts), 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 9. Long Memory, from the Nile to the Marketplace (edited drafts), 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 10. Noah, Joseph and Market Bubbles (edited drafts), 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 11. Multifractal Nature of Trading Time (edited drafts), 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folders 2-3)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 12. Ten Heresies of Finance (edited drafts), 2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Chapter 13. In the Lab (edited drafts), 2004 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Bibliography (draft 3, edited), 2004 Feb 19 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - opening pages (edited), 2004 Apr-May (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - clean galley, 2004 Jun 10 (Box 52, Folders 8-9)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - corrections by RLH (photocopy) - partial draft, 2004 Jun (Box 315, Folder 15)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - book reviews, 2004 (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - press, 2004-2005 (Box 315, Folder 13)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - Press for German version ( Fraktale und Finanzen), 2005 (Half-box 326, Folder 1)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - notes on book jacket, undated (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - The (Mis)Behavior of Markets: A Fractal View of Financial Turbulence - book jacket draft, undated (Box 315, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 6. The Fractalist: Memoir of a Scientific Maverick, circa 2003-2010
    This subseries consists of materials related to The Fractalist: Memoir of a Scientific Maverick, published in 2012. Materials include edited drafts and notes related to the many iterations of his biography. This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - Lone Ride - edited partial manuscript and computer printout drafts, circa 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice - edited partial computer printout draft, circa 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folders 1-2)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice - edited partial computer printout drafts, circa 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folders 3-5)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice (First Part of the Memoir of a Fractal Journey Through Roughness in the World, the Sciences, and the Arts) - edited partial manuscript and computer printout drafts, circa 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folders 1-5)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice (First Part of the Memoir of a Fractal Journey Through Roughness in the World, the Sciences, and the Arts) - edited partial manuscript and computer printout drafts, circa 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folders 1-4)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice - edited partial computer printout draft, circa 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice - heavily edited partial computer printout draft, circa 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lone Ride - edited partial computer printout draft, circa 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice - edited partial computer printout drafts, circa 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folders 4-5)
    - Lone Ride: The Apprentice - edited partial computer printout drafts, circa 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Lone Ride - heavily edited partial chapter drafts, circa 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Lone Ride - edited partial draft (computer printout) 2004 Jun 22 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lone Ride - heavily edited partial draft (computer printout) circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Lone Ride - edited partial draft (computer printout) circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lone Ride - edited computer printout circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)